Guide to the Ervin S. Hubbard glass plate negative collection, 1895-1901 MS2381
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Geographic locations, 1893-1901; Series 1
  - Unidentified locations, Series 1 Subseries 4
    - Unidentified Location, Carriages and Coaches, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 24)
      Johnson Victoria; No. 154
    - Unidentified Location, Carriages and Coaches, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 25)
      Child Coah; No. 156
    - Unidentified Location, Carriages and Coaches, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 26)
    - Unidentified Location, Carriages and Coaches, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 27)
    - Unidentified Location, Carriage Lamp, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 28)
      3/4 min exposure; indoors at noon; velox
    - Unidentified Location, Cemetery, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 29)
      Lawton Grave Monument; No. 16; Velox 1 min - 30 sec
    - Unidentified Location, Cemetery, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 23, Item 1)
    - Unidentified Location, Cemetery, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 23, Item 2)
    - Unidentified Location, Children in front of a ramshackle house, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 15, Item 30)
    - Unidentified Location, Clouds, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 23, Item 3)
      Part of building on the horizon
    - Unidentified Location, Clouds, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 23, Item 4)
    - Unidentified Location, Cow in Pasture, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 1)
    - Unidentified Location, Dog Among Plants Outside, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 2)
    - Unidentified Location, Flight Box, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 3)
      Wachusett Loft
    - Unidentified Location, Flight Box, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 4)
    - Unidentified Location, Flight Box, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 5)
    - Unidentified Location, Flight Box, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 6)
    - Unidentified Location, Flight Box, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 7)
    - Unidentified Location, Flowers in Vase, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 23, Item 5)
    - Unidentified Location, Footpath, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 8)
    - Unidentified Location, Landscape, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 23, Item 6)
      Big tree on canal
    - Unidentified Location, Landscape, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 23, Item 7)
      Footpath along a river
    - Unidentified Location, Landscape, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 9)
      Forrest
    - Unidentified Location, Landscape, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 10)
      Marsh-like landscape
    - Unidentified Location, Landscape, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 23, Item 8)
      People in a rocky landscape
    - Unidentified Location, Landscape, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 23, Item 9)
      Reflection in water
    - Unidentified Location, Landscape, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 23, Item 10)
    - Unidentified Location, Landscape, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 23, Item 11)
      River amid rocky landscape
    - Unidentified Location, Landscape, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 23, Item 12)
    - Unidentified Location, Landscape, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 23, Item 13)
    - Unidentified Location, Landscape, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 23, Item 14)
    - Unidentified Location, Landscape, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 23, Item 15)
      River with building in the background
    - Unidentified Location, Landscape, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 11)
      River
    - Unidentified Location, Landscape, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 12)
    - Unidentified Location, Landscape, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 13)
    - Unidentified Location, Landscape, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 23, Item 16)
      Rocky landscape with wooden structures
    - Unidentified Location, Landscape, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 23, Item 17)
    - Unidentified Location, Landscape, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 14)
      Shoreline
    - Unidentified Location, Landscape, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 23, Item 18)
      Small waterfall
    - Unidentified Location, Landscape, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 23, Item 19)
      Sunset on water with boat
    - Unidentified Location, Landscape, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 23, Item 20)
      View from underneath a bridge
    - Unidentified Location, Landscape, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 15)
    - Unidentified Location, Man atop Rock, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 16)
    - Unidentified Location, Man in Hammock, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 17)
    - Unidentified Location, Man in Rocky Landscape, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 18)
    - Unidentified Location, Man and Woman on a Porch, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 19)
    - Unidentified Location, Military Road, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 20)
    - Unidentified Location, Photograph of Drawing of George Washington, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 21)
    - Unidentified Location, The Power City, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 22)
      from suspension bridge; velox - 2 min 45 sec
    - Unidentified Location, Residence Exterior, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 23)
      House of Deputy Commissioner of Pensions; No. 33
    - Unidentified Location, Residence Exterior, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 24)
      In the woods
    - Unidentified Location, Residence Exterior, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 25)
      Residence with watchtower; Exterior of a home from the front
    - Unidentified Location, Residence Exterior, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 26)
      Residence with watchtower
    - Unidentified Location, Residence Exterior, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 27)
    - Unidentified Location, Residence Exterior, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 28)
      On the Shoreline
    - Unidentified Location, Residence Exterior, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 29)
    - Unidentified Location, Residence Exterior, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 5, Box 16, Item 30)
    - Unidentified Location, Residence Exterior, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 1)
    - Unidentified Location, Residence Exterior, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 2)
    - Unidentified Location, Residence Interior, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 3)
      Dressing Room
    - Unidentified Location, Residence Interior, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 4)
      Tea party in home interior
    - Unidentified Location, Residence Interior, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 5)
      Woman reading in home interior
    - Unidentified Location, Residence Interior, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 6)
    - Unidentified Location, Room Interior, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 7)
    - Unidentified Location, Roses in Vase, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 8)
    - Unidentified Location, Soldiers with cannons in front of a building, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 6, Box 24, Item 1)
    - Unidentified Location, Statue, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 9)
    - Unidentified Location, Stone Gazebo, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 6, Box 24, Item 2)
    - Unidentified Location, Street View, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 10)
    - Unidentified Location, Three People atop a Rock, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 11)
    - Unidentified Location, Wagons, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4; Glass plate negative is broken--please handle with care. (Carton 7, Box 26, Item 11)
      Toy or model wagons
    - Unidentified Location, Washington's Coat of Arms, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 12)
    - Unidentified Location, Waterfall, Undated; Series 1, Sub Series 4 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 13)
- Portraits, 1893-1894; Series 2
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  This series contains glass plate negatives of portraits photographed by Hubbard. The material in this series remains undated. Hubbard photographed his subjects in various locations: some in a studio-like setting and others in a residence or outside. The subjects of these images include portraits of his family, including wife Sarah Prescott Hubbard, daughter Helen Hubbard Lawton, son Laurence Hubbard, and son-in-law J. Edwin Lawton. Other portraits depict boat crew members, other identified people, and unidentified people.
  - Annie and Susie, 1893 September; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 14)
    Annie and Susie Lying on the grass; 21-8; 15
  - Birdie Standing by the mantle, 1893 September; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 15)
    Calais, ME; 20-10
  - Birdie, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 16)
    Side view; Calais, ME; 20-14
  - B.H.S. Girls, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 17)
    No. 26; Velox - 1 min 15 sec.
  - B.H.S. Group, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 18)
    No. 27; Velox - 1 min 30 sec.
  - Captain, Jennie Lippit, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 19)
    No. 11
  - Captain, Jennie Lippit, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 20)
    No. 12
  - Don, Bill, Boots, also 2nd. Mate, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 21)
    No. 6
  - Don Clarke, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 22)
    No. 133
  - Don on stern of Daisy, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 23)
    No. 31
  - Ed dressed as a tramp, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 24)
    No. 151
  - Edna Hardy, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 25)
    No. 37
  - Edna Hardy and Beulah, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 26)
    No. 38
  - Evelyn Booth, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 27)
    Flashlight; 25 sec; Carlow "1 min 15"; ISO plates
  - Father, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 28)
    No. 24
  - Father and Lee Warren, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 29)
    No. 144
  - Frank and Edna, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 17, Item 30)
    No. 43
  - Group at Mr. Hardy's, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 2)
    No. 42
  - Helen and Laurence, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 24, Item 3)
    Mr. Hubord; lead unmounted; Friday; 65; 2115
  - Helen and Laurie, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 3)
    copy; 20-1
  - J. Edwin Lawton, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 4)
    J. Edwin Lawton with salesman's models from E.T. Lawton; Carriage and Wagon builder; at 2210 M St., Georgetown
  - Laurence Hubbard sitting in chair, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 24, Item 4)
  - Laurie blowing bubbles, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 24, Item 5)
  - Laurie blowing bubbles, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 24, Item 6)
  - Laurie, 1894 February; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 5)
    Lawrie sitting inside the stool; 20-4
  - Lottie Gheen, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 6)
    No. 71
  - Mary Reily, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 7)
    Alias--Mrs. Sheridan; No. 18
  - Miss Fugitt, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 8)
    No. 72
  - Miss Fugitt, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 9)
    No. 73
  - Miss Robinette "The Younger", Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 10)
    No. 105; Arundle on the Bay
  - Miss Robinette "The Younger", Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 11)
    No. 109
  - Mr. and Mrs. Grant, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 12)
    No. 78
  - Mr. and Mrs. Grant, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 13)
    No. 79
  - Mr. and Mrs. Grant, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 14)
    No. 80
  - Mr. and Mrs. Hardy, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 15)
    No. 44
  - Mr. Dow Mattison, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 16)
    No. 20
  - Mr. Hackney, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 17)
    No. 145
  - Mr. Hackney, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 18)
    No. 146
  - Mr. Hardy, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 19)
    No. 36
  - Parsons and Weideman, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 20)
    No. 88; Trip of N.N.C.
  - "Rastus", Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 21)
    No. 92; Alias "Ambush" Mrs. Plyers; Velox 2m.
  - Sarah Prescott Hubbard, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 24, Item 7)
  - Sarah Prescott Hubbard, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 24, Item 8)
    Prescott Home in New Brunswick
  - Thomas Family, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 22)
    No. 25
  - Tommy Robinette, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 23)
    No. 110; Arundle on the Bay
  - Will and Birdie in Parlor, 1893 September; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 24)
    Calais, ME; 20-8
  - Will and Birdie in Sitting Room, 1893 September; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 25)
    Calais, ME
  - Group Portrait, in bow of Ice Schooner, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 26)
    No. 7
  - Group Portrait, on bridge with bikes, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 27)
  - Group Portrait, at a campsite, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 28)
  - Group Portrait, Canal-boat group, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 29)
  - Group Portrait, "Current Topic Club", Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 30)
    No. 67; at Marshall Hall
  - Group Portrait, "Current Topic Club", Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 18, Item 1)
    No. 85; at Chevy Chase
  - Group Portrait, "Current Topic Club", Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 2)
    No. 86; at Chevy Chase
  - Group Portrait, "Current Topic Club", Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 3)
    No. 87; at Chevy Chase
  - Group Portrait, Cyclists sitting outside, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 4)
  - Group Portrait, Eight children in front of home, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 24, Item 9)
  - Group Portrait, Five people at a beach, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 5)
  - Group Portrait, "The Four" in Fancy Dress, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 24, Item 10)
    Helen Hubbard (2nd from right) with three school friends
  - Group Portrait, "The Four" in Fancy Dress, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 24, Item 11)
  - Group Portrait, "The Four" in Fancy Dress, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 24, Item 12)
  - Group Portrait, "The Four" at Tea, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 24, Item 13)
  - Group Portrait, "The Four" at Tea, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 24, Item 14)
  - Group Portrait, "The Four" at Tea, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 24, Item 15)
  - Group Portrait, "The Four" at Tea, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 24, Item 16)
  - Group Portrait, Five women in a field of flowers, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 6)
  - Group Portrait, Four people at Cumberland, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 7)
    No. 13
  - Group Portrait, Four people on a boat, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 8)
  - Group Portrait, Four people on Horseback, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 9)
  - Group Portrait, Four women amid foliage, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 10)
  - Group Portrait, Four women, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 24, Item 17)
  - Group Portrait, "Group of F!", Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 24, Item 18)
  - Group Portrait, Hubbard Family, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 24, Item 19)
  - Group Portrait, Man and child examining a stone wall, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 11)
  - Group Portrait, Man shaving another man's beard, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 12)
  - Group Portrait, Man tying/brushing a woman's hair, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 13)
  - Group Portrait, Man and woman in a field, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 14)
  - Group Portrait, Man and woman on footpath, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 15)
  - Group Portrait, Men sitting on chairs outside, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 16)
  - Group Portrait, Men sitting on chairs outside, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 17)
  - Group Portrait, Men sitting on chairs outside, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 18)
  - Group Portrait, Men and women on a rocky beach, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 19)
  - Group Portrait, Old Crowd at Chevy Chase Lake, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 24, Item 20)
  - Group Portrait, Outside, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 20)
  - Group Portrait, Officers on Steamer Sue, 1898 July 30; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 21)
    Captain Gurley (Pro team); 1st officer; Purser Jones
  - Group Portrait, Picnic Outside, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 22)
  - Group Portrait, Seven people sitting outside, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 23)
  - Group Portrait, Seven Women in a bed, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 24)
  - Group Portrait, sitting on bridge railing, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 25)
  - Group Portrait, Six children outside, one in a tree, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 26)
  - Group Portrait, Ten people on a boat, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 27)
  - Group Portrait, Three men eating on boat, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 28)
  - Group Portrait, Three people on horses, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 29)
  - Group Portrait, Two children hugging, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 30)
  - Group Portrait, Two girls in front of brick wall, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 19, Item 1)
  - Group Portrait, Two girls in front of home exterior, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 2)
  - Group Portrait, Two girls in front of home exterior, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 3)
  - Group Portrait, Two girls in front of home exterior, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 4)
  - Group Portrait, Two girls in front of home exterior, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 5)
  - Group Portrait, Two girls, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 6)
  - Group Portrait, Two men in a canoe, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 7)
  - Group Portrait, Two women posing by a tree, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 8)
  - Group Portrait, Two women, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 9)
  - Portrait, Child in hammock, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 10)
  - Portrait, Child standing on chair, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 11)
  - Portrait, Girl in front of home exterior, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 12)
  - Portrait, Girl in front of home exterior, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 13)
  - Portrait, Girl posing while lying on grass, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 14)
  - Portrait, Girl, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 7, Box 25, Item 1)
  - Portrait, Girl, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 7, Box 25, Item 2)
  - Portrait, Man on a boat, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 15)
  - Portrait, Man with gun and two dogs, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 16)
  - Portrait, Man sitting on a boat, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 17)
  - Portrait, Man, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 18)
  - Portrait, Man, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 19)
  - Portrait, Man, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 20)
  - Portrait, Woman posing in between two trees, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 7, Box 25, Item 3)
  - Portrait, Woman posing on a tree branch, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 21)
  - Portrait, Woman posing with pitcher in landscape, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 7, Box 25, Item 4)
  - Portrait, Woman standing on footpath, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 22)
  - Portrait, Woman, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 23)
  - Portrait, Young Girl, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 7, Box 25, Item 5)
  - Portrait, Young Girl, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 7, Box 25, Item 6)
  - Portrait, Young Girl, Undated; Series 2 (Carton 7, Box 25, Item 7)
  - Poster, "Blackville Choir", Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 24)
  - Poster, "Honey, does you lub yo man?", Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 25)
  - Poster, "Honey, does you lub yo man?", Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 26)
  - Poster, "Mr. Johnsing, turn me luse", Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 27)
  - Poster, "Summer Days Will Come Again", Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 28)
    From bill poster
  - Poster, "Up to Snuff.", Undated; Series 2 (Carton 6, Box 20, Item 29)
    From watercolor